Jane Fonda papers SSC.MS.00477
Sophia Smith Collection
- Audiovisual materials, 1970-2014; 6; 37.88 linear feet (55 boxes)
  - Interviews/TV, Tape 2 - Maria Shriver interview and Rona Barrett interview as well as local news clip re: JF intro of clothes line, See inside label for sequence, approximately 1970-2016; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Ted Turner Interview with Carl Sagan, 1989 May 5-June 20; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, This Is Your Life, Show #112, Dr. Mimi Silbert (w/ Jane Fonda) Revised, 1984 June 5; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, '"To Jane" A Message of Love and Support from the Women's Group in Waterbury, CT, approximately 1989-1990; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, "The Tonight Show" with Jane Fonda, 1989 September 15; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, A Tribute to Stuart Karl, The Stuart Karl Foundation, approximately 1991; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, A Tribute to Vaclav Havel, approximately 1990-1995; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Untitled, approximately 1970-2016; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Untitled, approximately 1970-2016; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, USA-101-33AA We Are The World-USA for Africa, 1985 March 21; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Václav Havel's "Largo Desolato", 1984; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Vietnam Reconciliation Project, (Mar '93 – Vietnam) Excerpts: Gen Giap, Hanoi Hannah, Mr Vu (Former VC), Hanoi Hilton (for Private use of Ms Fonda), 1993; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Vote Yes on 128 - Big Green, approximately 1990; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, We Are the World: The Story Behind the Song, USA for Africa, 1985 May 5; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Country Joe Sings Resist, approximately 1971; 1 items (10" LP Album); 1 items (no file) (Box 81)
  - Interviews/TV, Kick-ass woman: A Tribute to: Jane Fonda, approximately 1970-2016; 1 items (Audio cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 81)
  - Interviews/TV, Rehm Show, Jane Fonda 'My Life So Far", 2005 April 15; 1 items (Audio cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 81)
  - Interviews/TV, Entrevista a Jane Fonda por Silvia Lemus, 1988 January 23; 1 items (1/2" Betamax video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 81)
  - Interviews/TV, GO TV Meeting, Part II, Sam, Jan, Pam, Rich, 1977 May 30; 1 items (1/2" Sanyo video cassette V-60); 1 items (no file) (Box 81)
  - Interviews/TV: 9th Annual People's Choice Awards Acceptance, Tie Katharine Hepburn and Jane Fonda, approximately 1983; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: 54th Annual Academy Awards - 1982, Golden Pond Award, 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: Actors on Acting with Martin Sheen as Guest 5/84, Arthur Allan Seidelman-Host, 1984 May 1; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: Agriculture Task Force Hearings & Coverage, Reel #1, Time Code, 1985 May 6; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: Agriculture Task Force Hearings & Coverage, Reel #2, Time Code, 1985 May 6; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: American Portrait, Maggie Kuhn, approximately 1975-1995; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: Canadian News with Don North, approximately 1975-1995; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: City Lights, Host: Brian Lineham, Guest: Jane Fonda, Rollover, 1981 November 30; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: Columbia Pictures "Quiet on the Set, Filming Agnes of God" w/ subtitles, 1985 July 9; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: Conference de Presse: Old Gringo: Pt. 1, (60:00), 1989 June 15; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: Conference de Presse "Old Gringo" Pt. 2, 1989 June 16; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: "Dollmaker" International Sales Presentation, approximately 1983; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: "The Dollmaker: Part I of III, 1983 October 3; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: "The Dollmaker" Part II of III, 1983 October 3; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: "The Dollmaker" Part III of III, 1983 October 3; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 82)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 1 of 3, Exhibition Copy A, 1992 February 14; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 2 of 3, Exhibition Copy A, 1992 February 14; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 3 of 3, Exhibition Copy A, 1992 February 14; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 1 of 4, Copy of MB Dub Master, 1992 February 14; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 2 of 4, Copy of MB Dub Master, 1992 February 14; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 3 of 4, Copy of MB Dub Master, 1992 February 14; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 4 of 4, Copy of MB Dub Master, 1992 February 14; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Entertainment Tonite, Summer 85, Jane Fonda on Agnes of God and Laurel Springs, 1985; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Fly Right, IFFA Home Video, Final Version, Submaster, 1987 September 10; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Free the Army (Part 1) #2, approximately 1970-1975; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Free the Army (Part 2) #2, approximately 1970-1975; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Good Morning America, Henry Fonda 5 Part Interview, approximately 1980; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Good Morning America, Henry Fonda Series, 1980 January; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Henry Fonda: The Man and His Movies, approximately 1980; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Henry Fonda, Part 1-2-3-4-5, dub, approximately 1980; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: JF on Good Morning America, 5 Part Series, "Women Coming of Age," Prime Time Workout, approximately 1980; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 83)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda, 60 min, BBC Documentary on JF's Life Past to Present, In depth discussion of JF participation in Vietnam, approximately 2005; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda BBC Documentary of Past and Present of Life of Jane Omnibus, approximately 1979; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: '"Jane Fonda" BBC Presentation Past and Present Life of JF, PBS, 1979 November 12; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Interview on Japanese Television, approximately 1975-1980; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Interview on Japanese TV, FUJI TV, "Bokura Club", approximately 1975-1980; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Interview with Japanese Television "Morning Plaza" (NHK TV), approximately 1975-1980; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Interview with Ruiko Yoshida for Asahi T.V. Japan, 1979 August; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Interviews - Rollover "Bob Maclean" Toronto, Canada, 1981 November; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Interviews with Ricard Rocha; Mexico TV, 1981 August 28; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda News Clips from 5 Different News Station, Intro of Clothing Line around Controversy, approximately 1975-2016; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Television Spot for New and Improved Workout, Tape and Record, approximately 1980-2016; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda's Advanced Workout, approximately 1980-2016; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda's Complete Workout: Jane Fonda Opening: Original, 1988 July 1; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: "Julia" "Typewriter" scene "Bench" scene from "Julia", 1978 October 5; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: "McClean at Large; Jane Fonda", Interview in Toronto Canada, Rollover, 1981 November; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: The Morning Show in Philadelphia: Tom Hayden and JF Introduce the Concept of Economic Democracy, 1979 October 9; 1 items (3/4" U-matic video cassettes); 1 items (no file) (Box 84)
  - Interviews/TV: Mr. Ha Van Lau, President, Vietnam Veteran Tourism Services, in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, March 1993; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: Muhammend [sic] Ali denial to be drafted with an army officials way of handling a resistant of the draft process, approximately 1971; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: Old Gringo, foreign trailer, Final, N/G 1-Lite Pix/Final Mix, 15 June 1989; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: Old Gringo: Last Day Shoot Celebration, approximately 1989; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: "Old Gringo" Part I, Unedited Material, 15 June 1989; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: "Old Gringo" Part II, Unedited Material, 15 June 1989; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: Old Gringo (trailer): Version 2, 17 May 1989; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: Rollover---Jane Fonda: 1 hour show with host Brian Linehan, Toronto, Canada, 30 Nov 1981; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: "That's Hollywood" "Fonda & Family", 1982; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: "Three Mile Island" Real People segment on Tim and Lisa Landis living near three mile island and their feelings about it, approximately 1989; 1 items (3/4" U-matic Video Cassettes) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: 8th Annual People's Choice Awards-Jane Fonda Acceptance, approximately 1982; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 85)
  - Interviews/TV: Close Captioning An Introduction to this Breakthrough by ABC News, Deaf and Hearing Impaired, approximately 1980-1989; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes) (Box 86)
  - Interviews/TV: Henry Fonda/AFI, Entire Fonda Acceptance Speech, #8A, approximately 1981; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes) (Box 86)
  - Interviews/TV: Henry Fonda Obit, 'Today' Version, approximately 1982; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 86)
  - Interviews/TV: JF on Evening Magazine Discuss Middle Age and P.R. on Book "Women Coming of Age", approximately 1978-1985; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes) (Box 86)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Interview w/ Jan Holmes WCUB TV (ABC) Boston "Rollover", 06 Dec 1981; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes) (Box 86)
  - Interviews/TV: Ida Nudell -DUB-, approximately 1987; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes) (Box 87)
  - Interviews/TV: Nicaragua: What's Happening Anyway?, approximately 1979; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes) (Box 87)
  - Interviews/TV: The People's Choice Ward, Favorite Motion Picture Actress: Jane Fonda, Also footage on the award itself, made by Orrefors of Sweden, 1981; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes) (Box 87)
  - Interviews/TV: "The Toni Tennille Show" Jane Interview - Part I Show #4-80 Part II #5-80, approximately 1980; 1 items (3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes) (Box 87)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, 1975 San Francisco Film Festival, 25 Oct 1975; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, A Radio for Construction of Citizenship, Marielos Monzon, Guatemala, Nov 2003; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Al [McKegg]'s All-Nite Diner, Twelve Songs about Life After Dark, 2006-2007; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Banjohova Witness: Can I Bite a Witness, 2010; 1 items; 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Copy of Soya's Disc, approximately 1995-2015; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, The Diane Rehm Show, Hour 2: Jane Fonda: "Prime Time," WAMU 88.5 FM, 09 Aug 2011; 1 items (CD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, The Diane Rehm Show, Hour 2: Shyness and Social Anxiety, WAMU 88.5 FM, 09 Aug 2011; 1 items (CD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, G-CAPP Children's Advocacy Center, FCCAC, Powerpoint Presentation, approximately 1995-2010; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, In Finland w/ Prez. Book Tour, Jane Fonda Tarja Halosen vieraana Màntyniemessè 17.3.06 Knva Surí Lain, 2005; 1 items (CD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Jane Fonda and the Airmen at the Gates of Travis Air Force Base, Reported by Danny Smithson, 11 Sep 1971; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Jane Fonda Interview, 03 Aug 2004; 1 items (CD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Photo Service CD: p_601; Les Rencontres de la Librairie Sauramps et du Café des Femmes; "cafe des femmes" a la médiathèque E. Zola, 10 Oct 2005; 1 items (CD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Photo Service CD: p_703; Les Rencontres de la LIBRAIRIE SAURAMPS et du Café des Femmes; Dédicace à la librarie Sauramps, 10 Oct 2005; 1 items (CD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Shut 'Em All Down: A No-Nuke Rally, CD 1 of 2, 06 May 1979; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Shut 'Em All Down: A No-Nuke Rally, CD 2 of 2, 06 May 1979; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV: audio recording: CDs, Stereo Total "Do The Bambi, 2005; 1 items (CD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: 49th Annual Academy Awards, Doc Feature: Barbara Kopple, Intro to Lilian Hellman, approximately 1977; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: After Lately, E!, Jane Fonda, 29 Jan 2012; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Clive James Meets Jane Fonda, approximately 1989; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: The Conversation, Episode 101, Sweetened CTM, Final Air Copy, 30 Apr 2012; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: David Sheehan, Oscar Show, 1978; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: David Sheehan with Oscar Nominee Jane Fonda, Doing some PR, approximately 1978; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: for auction benefiting solar energy, approximately 1990-2016; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Easter Bonnet Competition 23, 27 Apr 2009; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Friday Night with Jonathan Ross, Series 8 Show 11, 03 June 2005; 1 items (DVD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Fonda 70th Birthday, 2007; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: G-CAPP Premiere Retrospective, 2005; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda 70th, G-CAPP, 2007; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda, April 8 - April 27, Broadcast Clippings, approximately 1960-2016; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda at Los Angeles City College, 07 Apr 1976; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda, Charlie Rose, 16 Aug 2011; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda DVD Segments, 05 Apr 2012; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda Footage, Reel 3, 1) To See Vietnam 2) Bombing of Hanoi & Haiphong 3) Ida Nudel, 25 May 2004; 1 items (DVD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda Footage, Reel #03 Pt. 2, 1) Ida Nudel, 04 June 2004; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda Footage, Reel 5, 1) The Last Resort, 26 May 2004; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda Footage, Reel 6, Unidentified Farmworkers Film *Beginning of Film is Missing*, 26 May 2004; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda GMA (w/ promo), 08 Aug 2011; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda Golden Globes Coverage, The Insider, E! News, ET, Access Hollywood, 2012; 1 items (DVD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda, Joy Behar, 10 Aug 2011; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda, Letterman, 06 June 2012; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda Speaks Out on Workout, 1985; 1 items (DVD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda, TODAY, 06 June 2012; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda, TODAY, 08 June 2012; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Jane Fonda-Tonight Show, 12 Aug 2011; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Joy Behar, Jane Fonda, 09 Dec 2011; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: L'Oréal Paris, Mother's Day, Jane, Movie Picture Print, 04 Nov 2008; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Makers, Women in Hollywood, approximately 2014; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Nightline, Jane Fonda, 08 Aug 2011; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Regis and Kelly, Jane Fonda, 08 Aug 2011; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: The Simpsons, "Opposites A-Frack", 2014; 1 items (DVD); 1 items (Related manuscript, 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: V is for Vote, approximately 2000-2008; 1 items (DVD); 1 items (Related manuscript, Box 75) (Box 92)
  - Interviews/TV, video recording: Women's E news, 21 Leaders for the 21st Century: The stories of these remarkable newsmakers in their own words, 2004; 1 items (DVD) (Box 92)
- Memorabilia, 1955-2000; 7; 0.75 linear feet (2 boxes)
  The Memorabilia series contains various items, including a urinal sticker, a presentation poster, a flattened aluminum can that is painted with a likeness of Fonda, a Life magazine with Fonda on the cover, a NARAL Pro-Choice Georgia license plate, artwork featuring Fonda, and a cloth hat with a patch that states "Veteran of the 60's" and has multiple political buttons attached. There are oversize items.
  - Hanoi Jane's Urinal Stickers, 1975-2015; 1 folders (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - G-CAPP Genius [drawing of Jane Fonda on a flattened can], 1980-2010; 1 folders (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Education, Jane Fonda and Timothy E. Wirth Presentation, 2000; 1 folders (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - 20ans Magazine, 1972 August; 1 folders (1 magazine) (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Interview Magazine, 1984 March; 1 folders (1 magazine) (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Ladies Home Journal Magazine (cover), 1959 October; 1 folders (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Life Magazine, 6 June 1955; 1 folders (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Movie Digest Magazine, 1972 Sept; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Pageant Magazine, 1960 November; 1 folders (1 magazine) (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - NARAL Pro-Choice Georgia [license plate], 2000-2015; 1 folders (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - [Unknown artist and title artwork, 20 Jane Fonda vignettes], approximately 1980-2015; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Veteran of the 60's [hat], 1970-2000; 1 boxes (Box 94)